+65 9793 3811

<u>Junhao.h95@gmail.com</u>

<u>https://linkedin.com/in/hjh1995</u>

https://junhao-h.github.io/portfolio

# Ho Jun Hao

#### Summary

Creative Developer that is passionate about both art and design. Experienced with the design and development process for both games and web projects. Familiar with numerous programming languages including C, C++, C#, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, and Python. Enjoy exploring emergent technologies to create a unique visual and interactive digital experience.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Problem Solver
- Creative
- Innovative

- Game Design
- UI/UX Design
- Team player
- Unreal Engine
- Unity
- Communication

## **Experience**

**Unreal Engine & Front-end Developer Intern** - 01/2023 to 04/2023 **INSPIFY**, Singapore

- Create a Mercedes-Benz 3D immersive experience with Unreal Engine 5.1 and stream it in the browser using Pixel Streaming
- Design and develop and iterate the responsive user interface on web, by layer the web interface over the pixel stream using React and CSS.

Full Stack Developer Intern - 09/2022 to 12/2022

**Grow Financial**, Singapore

- Cooperate with designers to create clean user interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front-end and back-end code delivery.

Surveillance System Engineer- 03/2015 to 08/2015

ST Engineering, Singapore

- Design and set up video surveillance systems for the Downtown Line MRT station.
- Monitor, inspect and correct the final product to meet established quality standards.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Science in **Computer Science and Game Design** - 2023 **DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore**, SG